RG 062:099, Town of North Branford
Connecticut State Library
Town of North Branford records
1830-1978
Connecticut State Library
North Branford (Conn.)
18.5 cubic feet
Tax and school records for the town of North Branford.
RG062_099
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of North Branford was incorporated in May 1831 and was taken from Branford.
Scope and Content
Tax and school records for the town of North Branford.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- North Branford -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- North Branford -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- North Branford -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- North Branford -- Registers; Schools -- Connecticut -- North Branford -- History -- Sources
Places:
North Branford (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1830-1978
  - T001126
    - Tax abstracts, 1830-1978; 138 volumes
      Volumes for years 1914-1978 are not boxed.
      Northford is the Second Society of North Branford. Prior to 1909 there were separate volumes for the First and Second Societies. The earlier of these are labeled Northford and the later Second Society.
      - Branford, Second Society, 1830 (Box Box 1)
      - First Society, 1831 (Box Box 1)
      - Northford, 1831 (Box Box 1)
      - First Society, 1832 (Box Box 1)
      - Northford, 1832 (Box Box 1)
      - First Society, 1833 (Box Box 1)
      - Northford, 1833 (Box Box 1)
      - First Society, 1834 (Box Box 1)
      - Northford, 1834 (Box Box 1)
      - First Society, 1835 (Box Box 1)
      - Northford, 1835 (Box Box 1)
      - North Branford, First Society, 1836 (Box Box 1)
      - Northford, 1836 (Box Box 1)
      - North Branford, First Society, 1837 (Box Box 1)
      - Northford, 1837 (Box Box 1)
      - North Branford, 1838 (Box Box 1)
      - Northford, 1838 (Box Box 1)
      - North Branford, First Society, 1839 (Box Box 1)
      - Northford, 1839 (Box Box 1)
      - North Branford, First Society, 1840 (Box Box 1)
      - Northford, 1840 (Box Box 1)
      - North Branford, First Society, 1841 (Box Box 2)
      - Northford, 1841 (Box Box 2)
      - Northford, 1841 April 20 (Box Box 2)
      - First Society, 1842 (Box Box 2)
      - Second Society, 1842 (Box Box 2)
      - First Society, 1843 (Box Box 2)
      - Second Society, 1843 (Box Box 2)
      - First Society, 1844 (Box Box 2)
      - Second Society, 1844 (Box Box 2)
      - First Society, 1845 (Box Box 2)
      - Second Society, 1845 (Box Box 2)
      - First Society, 1846 (Box Box 2)
      - Second Society, 1846 (Box Box 2)
      - First Society, 1847 (Box Box 2)
      - Second Society, 1847 (Box Box 2)
      - First Society, 1848 (Box Box 2)
      - Second Society, 1848 (Box Box 2)
      - First Society, 1849 (Box Box 2)
      - Second Society, 1849 (Box Box 2)
      - First Society, 1850 (Box Box 3)
      - Second Society, 1850 (Box Box 3)
      - First Society, 1851 (Box Box 3)
      - First Society, 1852 (Box Box 3)
      - Second Society, 1852 (Box Box 3)
      - First Society, 1853 (Box Box 3)
      - Second Society, 1853 (Box Box 3)
      - First Society, 1854 (Box Box 3)
      - Second Society, 1854 (Box Box 3)
      - First Society, 1855-1858 (Box Box 3)
      - First Society, 1859 (Box Box 3)
      - Second Society, 1860 (Box Box 4)
      - First Society, 1863-1867 (Box Box 4)
      - Second Society, 1864-1867 (Box Box 4)
      - Second Society, 1868-1872 (Box Box 4)
      - Second Society, 1868-1871 (Box Box 4)
      - Second Society, 1872-1877 (Box Box 4)
      - Second Society, 1873-1877 (Box Box 4)
      - Second Society, 1878 (Box Box 5)
      - First Society, 1878-1880 (Box Box 5)
      - First Society, 1881-1882 (Box Box 5)
      - First Society, 1884-1886 (Box Box 5)
      - Second Society, 1884-1887 (Box Box 5)
      - First Society, 1887-1891 (Box Box 5)
      - Second Society, 1888-1891 (Box Box 5)
      - First Society, 1892-1896 (Box Box 6)
      - Second Society, 1892-1896 (Box Box 6)
      - First Society, 1897-1899 (Box Box 6)
      - Second Society, 1897-1899 (Box Box 6)
      - First Society, 1900-1905 (Box Box 6)
      - Second Society, 1900-1904 (Box Box 6)
      - First Society, 1906-1908 (Box Box 7)
      - Second Society, 1905-1908 (Box Box 7)
      - 1909-1910 (Box Box 7)
      - 1911-1912 (Box Box 7)
      - 1913 (Box Box 7)
      - 1914, 1 volume
      - 1915, 1 volume
      - 1916, 1 volume
      - 1917, 1 volume
      - 1918, 1 volume
      - 1919, 1 volume
      - 1920, 1 volume
      - 1921, 1 volume
      - 1922, 1 volume
      - 1923, 1 volume
      - 1924, 1 volume
      - 1925, 1 volume
      - 1926, 1 volume
      - 1926, 1 volume
      - 1927, 1 volume
      - 1928, 1 volume
      - 1929, 1 volume
      - 1930, 1 volume
      - 1931, 1 volume
      - 1932, 1 volume
      - 1933, 1 volume
        Included are two tax exempt reports and two reports to the relief board to the tax commissioner.
      - 1934, 1 volume
      - 1935, 1 volume
      - 1936, 1 volume
      - 1937, 1 volume
      - 1938, 1 volume
      - 1939, 1 volume
      - 1940, 1 volume
      - 1941, 1 volume
      - 1942, 1 volume
      - 1943, 1 volume
      - 1944, 1 volume
      - 1945, 1 volume
      - 1946, 1 volume
      - 1947, 1 volume
      - 1948, 1 volume
      - 1949, 1 volume
      - 1950, 1 volume
      - 1951, 1 volume
      - 1952, 1 volume
      - 1953, 1 volume
      - 1954, 1 volume
      - 1955, 1 volume
      - 1956, 1 volume
      - 1957, 1 volume
      - 1958, 1 volume
      - 1959, 1 volume
      - 1960, 1 volume
      - 1961, 1 volume
      - 1962, 1 volume
      - 1963, 1 volume
      - 1964, 1 volume
      - 1965, 1 volume
      - 1966, 1 volume
      - 1967, 1 volume
      - 1968, 1 volume
      - 1969, 1 volume
      - 1970, 1 volume
      - 1971, 1 volume
      - 1972, 1 volume
      - 1973, 1 volume
      - 1974, 1 volume
      - 1975, 1 volume
      - 1976, 1 volume
      - 1977, 1 volume
      - 1978, 1 volume
  - T000293
    - North School District minute book, 1841-1905 (Box Box 1)